回到线稿。在这个手机布局中，
Going back to the wire frames. In the phone layout, we
我们想要today项稍微大一点儿。
wanted the today item to be a little bit bigger. But on
但在平板中，我们希望他就跟其他项一样就好，
the tablets, we just want it to look like all the
因为我们还有一个展开面板在那儿。
other items, because we have an expanded detail pane here. To do
要在ForecastAdapter的newView方法中这么做，我们应当为列表项返回
this in the forecast adapter new view method, we should return
布局，而非为today返回
the layout for a list item forecast not for the today layout.
然后在bindView方法中，我们应当为today项
Then in the bind view method, for the today item, we
使用灰色图标，而不是有颜色的图标。
should use the gray icon instead of the colored icon. These decisions
这一决定由getItemViewType方法来控制。
get controlled by the return value of the getItemViewType method. Therefore,
因此，我们修改getItemViewType方法，这样在0的位置上，
we modify the getItemViewType method so that at the zero position,
如果我们必须使用特殊的today布局，
if we have to use the special today layout, then we
我们就返回view type为today。否则，如果我们不想用
return view type today. Otherwise, if we shouldn't use the special
特别的today布局，那我们只要返回所有将来日期
today layout, then we should just return the view type for
的view type就好。这个布尔值是由设值方法控制的。
all future days. This Boolean is controlled by the setter method.
要访问这一布尔值，我们在ForecastAdapter中创一个公共的设值方法。
To access this Boolean, we created a public setter method on
但是谁知道如何设置这个值属性呢？
the forecast adapter. But who knows how to set this value properly?
好，MainActivity会知道他是单面板
Well the main activity knows whether it's one pane,
还是双面板UI的。所以，他可以决定
or two pane UI. So, it can decide whether
我们该不该使用特定的today布局。
we should use the special today layout or not.
我们在此没有访问ForecastAdapter，但
We don't have access to the forecast adapter here, but
我们可以从ForecastFragment中取得其值。
we can plumb the value through the forecast fragment.
要访问ForecastFragment，我们可以
To get access to the forecast fragment, we can ask
请求FragmentManager，并把fragmentID传给他。
the fragment manager and pass it the fragment ID.
完成修改代码，于是app看起来就像这样。
Finish changing the code so the app looks like this.